(晴太)あれは… あの傷は…｡
That's...
Th-That scar...
They enforce Yoshiwara's laws and punish all who resist. The Hyakka.
(晴太)吉原と吉原の掟を犯す者を
処断する 自警団 百華｡
その百華を率いる
吉原最強の番人…｡
She's the leader, and the most powerful guard in Yoshiwara.
(月詠)月詠でありんす｡
I am Tsukuyo.
(新八/晴太)うわ～っ!!
Why?!
(新八)なんで!?
なんで ﾎﾞｸらが自警団に!?
Why are we being attacked by the defense force?!
知らねえよ！
I-I don't know!
This isn't the time! Get Seita out of here now!
(神楽)言ってる場合か！
晴太を早く連れていくね！
新ぱ…｡
Shinpa-
My target...
(月詠)わっちの狙いは➡
ぬしじゃ!!
is you!
(銀時)よぉ｡
ぎ…｡
Yo!
Gin...
待たせちまったな｡
Sorry for the wait.
["Beware of those who use an Umbrella on a sunny day!"]
U-Umm...
あ… あの…
すみません 銀さん｡
Excuse me, Gin-san.
あの… さ 刺さってます｡
You...
got...
stabbed.
え？ 何が？
By what?
いや… 今
完全に刺さってましたよね それ｡
Well...
You were definitely stabbed just now.
大丈夫ですか？
え？
Are you alright?
What are you talking about?
なに言ってんの
刺さってねえよ 何も｡ ほら｡
I wasn't stabbed by anything.
See?
Well, you're...
いや… 血だらけだし
ﾑﾘしないでください｡
You're covered in blood, so please don't push yourself.
大丈夫ですか ﾎﾝﾄ｡
Are you really alright?
だから 刺さってないって
言ってんじゃん｡
I'm telling you I wasn't stabbed.
これはあれだよ➡
This is... you know...
I got grazed, and it bled a little.
ちょっと かすって
血出たみたいな｡
断じて 刺さってないからね｡
いや でも…｡
I definitely wasn't stabbed.
No... but...
刺さってねえって
言ってんだろうが！
I'm telling you I wasn't stabbed!
Do you really want me to get stabbed that much?
そんなに お前
ｵﾚを刺したいか!!
Fine, I got it.
あぁ わかった!! じゃあ
刺さったことにしといてやるよ!!
Then let's just say I was stabbed!
Even though I wasn't actually stabbed!
刺さってないけどね ﾎﾝﾄは｡
いや 完全に刺さってましたよね｡
No, you really were stabbed.
いい加減にしろ お前！
Don't push your luck!
The one who was stabbed is saying he wasn't stabbed!
刺さってないって 刺さった本人が
言ってんだから➡
So let's just say I wasn't stabbed!
刺さってねえことで
いいだろうが!!
今 認めましたよね？
You just admitted it.
You know... you should... really...
あのさ お前さ ﾎﾝﾄにさ
空気読めよ｡
read the situation around you.
ここは 流せよ｡ ここは
刺さってない感じにしとこうよ｡
Just let this one slip.
Just pretend I wasn't stabbed.
ｵﾚ めっちゃ
かっこ悪いじゃん｡
It'll make me look really bad.
完全に 全部
打ち落とした顔してたじゃん｡
I even posed like I had just deflected all the attacks.
めっちゃ
恥ずかしいじゃん｡
This is totally embarrassing!
あ… やべえよ｡
Damn...
ｵﾚ ちょっと恥ずかしくて
振り向けねえよ｡
I'm too embarrassed to even turn around.
笑ってない？ みんな笑ってない？
大丈夫？
Are they laughing? Is everyone laughing at me? Is everything alright?
Yes, everything's alright.
大丈夫です｡
You were able to strike down all of the shots in my attack, who are you?
わっちの攻撃を
すべて 打ち落とすとは➡
何者じゃ ぬし｡
She's trying to help me out!
気い遣ってくれてる！
She's pretending that I struck them all down!
全部 打ち落としたことに
してくれてる！
いい娘だよ
あの娘 いい娘だよ｡
She's a good kid! She's definitely a good kid!
攻撃？ ｿｲﾂは悪かった｡
Attack?
Sorry about that.
ｵﾚは ｸﾅｲがのんびり
散歩してんのかと思ったよ｡
I thought those kunai were just taking a stroll.
どうだい
こんな物騒なﾓﾝより➡
How about it? Instead of these dangerous things,
ｵﾚと もっといいﾓﾝを刺し…｡
how about I use something better to sta-
Oh damn...
やべえよ｡ 腕にも刺さってた｡
見られた 今の完全に見られた｡
She got my hand too!
They saw it! They must have seen it!
You didn't strike them all down at all!
ｱﾝﾀ 結局
全然 打ち落とせてねえじゃん！
あちこち
刺されまくってんじゃん!!
You got stabbed all over the place!
This is bad. What should I do?
やばい どうしよう｡ 笑ってるだろ
ｱｲﾂら笑ってるだろ？
They're laughing at me. They're laughing at me, right?
That's it. I'm going home. I'm going to the hospital.
もうﾑﾘだ 帰るわ ｵﾚ｡ 病院行くわ｡
落ち着いてください｡
Please, just calm down.
打ち落とした感じにするから
恥ずかしいんですよ｡
It's embarrassing because you acted like you deflected everything.
身を挺して 晴太君
かばったことにしましょう｡
Let's just pretend that you were using your body to shield Seita-kun.
I'm impressed that you would use your body to shield the kid.
身を挺して 子供をかばうとは
たいしたﾔﾂ｡
ぬし 何者じゃ｡
Who are you?
She was listening to us!
聞いてくれた!!
計画 聞いてくれたよ！
She's going along with our plan!
いい娘だよ あの娘
やっぱり いい娘だよ！
She's a good kid! She really is a good kid!
なんて攻撃だ｡
盾になるのが 精一杯だったぜ｡
Your attack was something else.
It took all my strength just to shield him.
おい 大丈夫か｡ 晴太｡
Oi!
Are you alright, Seita?
Seita... kun...?
せい… た… 君？
ｳｿ!? え？ ｳｿ…｡
No way...
You're kidding!
(神楽)せ… 晴太…｡
S-Seita...
Seita!
(神楽)晴太!!
Gin-san! This!
銀さん これ！
ちょっ… これ!!
Look! He was totally stabbed!
刺さってますよ 完全に！
さっそうと助けに来て➡
You came here to save us, but he got stabbed anyway!
結局 思いきり
ﾌﾞｯ刺さってますよ!!
何しに来たんですか！ ｱﾝﾀ!?
What the hell did you come here for?!
ﾃﾒｴら…｡
You bastards...
You bastards!
ﾃﾒｴら 死ぬ覚悟は
できてんだろうな!!
I hope you're all prepared to die!
He's blaming them! He's pretending to be angry so that he can blame them!
ごまかした!! 怒って
結局 全部 他人のせいにした!!
≪(百華)あの…｡
Umm...
Umm... Excuse me, I saw the whole thing.
(百華)あの… すみません｡
私 見ちゃったんですけど｡
あの… さっき➡
Umm... Before, when that guy came to help,
あの人が
助けに入ったときに➡
one of the kunai that got deflected...
弾いた ｸﾅｲの１本が➡
刺さってました｡
stabbed him.
≪あの… 私も見た｡
≪あちきも｡
Uh...
I saw it too.
Me too.
≪わっちも｡
≪あれ 弾かなかったら➡
Me too.
If that kunai wasn't deflected, it wouldn't have hit him.
刺さってなかったよね｡
Then it's as if that man killed him.
≪え？ じゃあ
あの人が殺したようなもんじゃ｡
えっ 銀さん？
ちょっ… 銀さん？
Gin-san...?
Hey... Gin-san!
ﾃﾒｴら…｡
You bastards...
ﾃﾒｴら 死ぬ覚悟は
できてんだろうな!!
You bastards!
I hope you're all prepared to die!
He's pretending that whole conversation never happened and re-edited the scene!
なかったことにしてる!!
前のやりとり➡
丸々 なかったことにして
再編集しようとしてる!!
ぬしも わっちのｸﾅｲの
餌食となるがいい｡
You shall also fall prey to my kunai.
わっちが殺した
あのﾜｯﾊﾟのところに➡
You will soon be joining the kid I killed.
今すぐ 連れていってやろう｡
超 気い遣ってくれてるよ！
She's trying to help me so much!
She's taking the blame all by herself!
くどいくらい 自分が
やったことにしてくれてるよ!!
いい人だ！
あの人やっぱり いい人だ!!
She's a good person! She really is a good person!
あっ… ちょっと…➡
Wait...
もう それ以上 気い遣わないで…｡
Please stop helping me.
優しくされると
泣きそうになるから…｡
I'll feel like crying if you're this kind to me.
What the hell are you talking about?!
なに めんどくせえこと
言ってんだ～!!
I'm not helping you.
気いなど 遣っておらん｡
Had I not thrown those kunai, none of this would've happened.
わっちが ｸﾅｲを投げねば
こうは ならなかった…｡
過程は どうあれ
原因を作ったのは わっちじゃ｡
Regardless of how it happened, ultimately, I started it.
わっちが 殺した｡
I killed him.
Please stop. I understand how you feel, but I killed him.
やめて ﾎﾝﾄ！
お前の気持は わかったから！
ｵﾚが やったんだ～!!
なに？ この やりとり！
Why are you two consoling each other?!  You're both enemies!
ｱﾝﾀら 敵どうしだよね!?
I said that I killed him.
(月詠)わっちが やったと
言っとるんじゃ｡
No, it was me!
いや ｵﾚだ!!
(月詠)いや わっちじゃ！
No, it was me!
It was me!
Me!
ｵﾚ!!
(新八/神楽)えっ…？
ぎ… 銀さん!!
ぎ… 銀ちゃん!!
G-Gin-san!
(月詠)ﾔﾂらは
わっちが 全員 始末しんした｡
I took care of all of them.
(月詠)そう 鳳仙様に 伝えなんし｡
Go report to Housen-sama accordingly.
(月詠)後始末は
わっちが しておく…｡
I'll clean up here.
おい！
Oi!
起きなんし！
Get up.
If you don't move it,
さっさとせんと…
今度は 本物のｸﾅｲを叩き込むぞ｡
I'm going to use a real kunai on you.
あれ？ 生きてる…｡
We're still alive?
(月詠)門は 見張りがいる｡
There are people guarding the gate,
(月詠)この中を
通ってゆくがよいわ｡
so you should escape through here.
(月詠)１日半は かかるが
いずれ 外に出られるはずじゃ｡
It'll take you a day and a half, but you should eventually reach the surface.
(月詠)さっさと ここから逃げろ！
Get out of here quickly!
(月詠)次 来たら 本当に殺す！
If you come back again, I'll kill you for real.
部下どもを ひかせ➡
You sent your subordinates away and put up an act to let us escape?
ｵｲﾗたちを逃がすために
芝居を うったのか…!?
(晴太)百華の頭の ｱﾝﾀが…｡
Why would you, the leader of the Hyakka, do that?
わっちは 吉原の番人…➡
I am the guard of Yoshiwara.
吉原で 騒ぎを起こすﾔﾂは消す｡
I eliminate any problematic elements in Yoshiwara.
それだけで ありんす｡
That is all.
悪いが 消えることはできないし➡
Sorry, but we can't just disappear like this,
ｱﾝﾀらに 消される覚えもない！
and we don't intend to let you kill us either.
(晴太)ｵｲﾗは 母ちゃんに…➡
I'm only here to meet my mother, to meet Hinowa. That's all!
日輪太夫に 会いに来ただけだ！
だったら なおさら帰るがいい｡
Then I advise you to leave all the more.
わっちに ぬしらを逃がせと
頼んだのは 誰でもない｡
The one who asked me to let you guys off is none other than...
その 日輪じゃ｡
Hinowa herself.
(晴太)母ちゃんが…➡
Mother did?
Mother knows about me? She knows that I'm here?
(晴太)母ちゃん…
ｵｲﾗのことを 知っているのか!?
ｵｲﾗが ここに いることを…！
(月詠)吉原の楼主 鳳仙は➡
Housen, the owner of Yoshiwara, is afraid of letting you come into contact with Hinowa.
ぬしと日輪が 接触することを
恐れいなんし…｡
ここにいれば ぬしの命はない｡
Stay here, and you will lose your life.
(神楽)なんで!?
子供とﾏﾐｰが会うのを➡
Why? What reason does he have to stop a mother and her son from meeting?
邪魔立てされる義理は ないね!!
…日輪が 吉原から
逃げるかもしれんからじゃ｡
Because Hinowa may then try to escape from Yoshiwara.
(月詠)８年前…➡
Just like when she tried to escape with you when you were still a baby eight years ago.
赤子の ぬしを連れて
逃げたときのように…｡
ｵｲﾗを 連れて…｡
With me...
20年前…
侍と天人の争いによって➡
Twenty years ago, due to the war between the samurai and the Amantos,
吉原は 一度
地上から 姿を消した｡
Yoshiwara was razed to the ground.
だが
その利に目をつけた 天人たちが➡
However, the Amanto were interested in its potential profit and colluded with the Bakufu
幕府に取り入り
地中深く 復活させたのが➡
to secretly resurrect it underground,
ここ… 吉原桃源郷…｡
creating the Yoshiwara Tougenkyou.
(月詠)
中央暗部の関わりが あるゆえ➡
Because of its secret connections with the Central Administration,
ここは 幕府にも 黙殺される
超法規的空間…｡
it is ignored by the Bakufu and allowed to operate under its own jurisdiction.
Naturally, it became a place infested with the rich and powerful indulging themselves.
しぜん 公にできぬ
政の秘事を語る場所として➡
利用されることも多い…｡
つまり…
悪政を育む 温床となっている…｡
In other words, it is a breeding ground of corruption.
花魁ともなれば➡
Any courtesan knows at least one or two of the country's most confidential secrets.
国を 左右しかねない情報の
一つや二つ 知り得る…｡
ゆえに 遊女たちは
一度 入ったら 最後…➡
Because of this, the women who arrive are never allowed to see the Sun again.
お天道様を 拝むことは
二度と ない…｡
方々から
売り飛ばされてきた女たちは➡
Once they arrive here, they're treated like commercial entities.
商品として扱われ
地下に つながれ➡
They are bound to this cavern and are exploited until they become useless.
使い物に ならなくなるまで
酷使される…｡
Those that are no longer of any value are just thrown away.
価値が なくなれば
野たれ死に させられ➡
逃げ出そうとする者も
皆 始末される…｡
Those who try to escape are killed.
This place is not called the land of everlasting night...
この街が
常夜の街と呼ばれるのは➡
色里を指してのことではない｡
solely due to its rotten reputation.
そう… この街に売られて
初めて知った…｡
I only understood this once I was sold here.
わっちらには 決して➡
For us, the dawn of hope will never arrive.
希望に満ちた朝が
訪れることはない…｡
明けることのない絶望を…➡
We can only live a life of endless despair in an everlasting night.
終わることのない夜を➡
わっちらは
生きねばならないということを…｡
だが… そんな絶望のなか➡
However...
in the depths of this despair,
もののような目をした
女たちのなかで➡
amongst the women with lifeless eyes,
たった一人だけ…➡
there was one woman...
who had a different feel to her.
違う目をした女がいた…｡
((日輪:まぁ ｱﾝﾀ…
亀吉んとこの 禿だね？
You're the apprentice from Kamekichi's place, right?
(日輪)また あの女と
ｹﾝｶしたのかい？
Did you argue with that woman again?
あれは
なにかと 下の者に当たり散らす➡
She's a woman that loves to take out her anger on anyone around her.
嫌な女だからね｡
腹が立つのも わかるが➡
I know you can't stand her,
ｱﾝﾀも 姉様に逆らってばかりじゃ
そのうち 殺されちまうよ｡
but if you keep making her angry, you might die, you know!
ここは 子供にだって
容赦ないからね｡
Even children won't receive any mercy here.
そんな ふてぶてしい顔してるから
目え つけられちまうんだよ｡
You keep getting bullied because you always have that brazen look on your face.
かわいい顔してんだ…｡
You have an adorable face, give me a smile!
少しは 笑ってみな｡
いったい 何が
そんなに 気に食わないんだい？
What is it that you couldn't stand?
殺したきゃ 殺せばいいんじゃ！
Just let her kill me if she wants.
(月詠)こんな牢獄にいたら➡
In this prison,
わっちも お前らみたいに
死んだような目に なってしまう｡
I'll end up a lifeless husk like the rest of you anyway.
(月詠)
ものに なり果てるくらいなら➡
Instead of ending up as some guy's merchandise,
わっちゃ
殺されるほうが ﾏｼじゃ！
I'd rather be killed.
牢獄ね…｡
Prison, eh?
ｱﾝﾀ… 上に行けば➡
You think you'd be free if you were above ground?
自由に なれるとでも
思ってんのかい？
(日輪)ｱﾝﾀみたいなﾔﾂはね➡
With your outlook, you would never be free no matter where you went.
どこ行ったって
自由になんて なれやしないよ｡
(日輪)しょせん 人間なんざ➡
After all, humans...
地球って檻に入れられた ｴﾃ公さ｡
are locked in a prison known as Earth.
地上も地下も 変わりゃしないよ｡
Whether you're above or below ground makes no difference.
広いか 狭いかだけの話さね｡
It's just a question of wide or narrow.
檻が狭いだなんだ
ふてくされるﾔﾂは➡
People who feel that the prison is too narrow and can't take it...
そりゃ不自由だろうさ｡
will never be free.
鉄格子 見つめるだけの
生活してんだから｡
Theirs would be a life just watching the cell bars.
本当の不自由ってのはね…➡
In order to truly be caged,
自分で 心に
檻を張っちまうことさ｡
you have to set up a prison inside your own heart.
死ぬだなんだ わめいて
逃げ回ってるﾋﾏがあったら➡
If you have the energy to whine about dying or whatnot,
檻ん中で戦いな｡ ﾃﾒｴと…｡
why not fight it out in this very cell,
against yourself, that is.
But if there's one less noisy monkey around,
(日輪)その
うるさいｴﾃ公が いなくなりゃ➡
少しは 檻も
広く感じるだろうさ))
you might end up realizing that this cell is pretty spacious.
(月詠)女の目は
死んでいなかった｡
That woman's eyes were not lifeless.
((おい ちょっと聞いたかい？
Oi, have you heard?
A fight broke out between two prostitutes in the streets!
遊女同士が 通りで
殴り合いの大ｹﾞﾝｶだってよ｡
日輪が 亀吉に
ｹﾝｶ売ったって ﾎﾞｺﾎﾞｺだぜ｡
Hinowa picked a fight with Kamekichi. She's beat up pretty badly!
おお 怖い怖い｡
また なんだって？
Oh, scary!
What was it about this time?
気に食わないことでも
あったのかい？
What is it that pissed them off?
知りゃしねえよ
遊女の考えることなんざ…｡
Hell if I know.
Who knows what goes on in those prostitutes' heads...
(日輪)待ちな｡
折檻部屋に食事なんて運んだら➡
Wait.
If you bring food to the detention cell,
ｱﾝﾀも 折檻されるよ｡
you'll get reprimanded too.
(月詠)勘違いするな｡
これは 昨日➡
Don't be mistaken.
This is the stuff you left behind yesterday.
お前が 置いていったものじゃ｡
The rice balls that you made tasted so bad I couldn't eat it.
お前らの握ったﾒｼなんて
まずくて食えやしんせん｡
お前のものを返しただけじゃ｡
I'm just returning what belongs to you.
わっちは 何も
悪いことはしていない｡
I'm not doing anything wrong.
そうかい｡
Is that so?
あたしゃ 握り飯 作るの
こんなに上手かったかね？
I don't recall my rice balls being this good.
(日輪)ちょいと こっちに来て
食べさせてくれないかい？
Can you come over and help feed them to me?
手が使えないんだ｡
I can't use my hands.
いいの？
(日輪)構いやしないさ｡
Can I?
I don't mind.
禿は 姉さまの
世話をするのが仕事だ｡
Apprentices are supposed to serve courtesans anyway.
今日から 私が ｱﾝﾀの姉さまだ))
From today onwards, I'll be your big sister.
(月詠)常夜の
闇の中にいた わっちに➡
I was in the darkness of the everlasting night,
小さな太陽ができた｡
わっちだけじゃない｡
but I found a miniature sun.
Not just me,
死んだような目をしていた
女たちも➡
it was the same for the other lifeless women.
あの女の陽気な笑顔に
ふれるときだけは➡
When they saw her radiant smile,
皆 自然と 顔がほころんだ｡
they too naturally begin to smile.
やがて その小さな太陽は
この吉原を照らす➡
Not long after, that small sun...
grew and eventually illuminated all of Yoshiwara.
大きな光となった｡
そう… それが 日輪｡
That's right,
that is Hinowa.
わっちが 己が顔を傷つけ
女を捨てたのは➡
I cut my face and gave up my right to live as a woman...
花魁になるのが
嫌だったわけでも➡
not because I disliked becoming a courtesan,
百華として
吉原を守るためでもない｡
nor because I wanted to become a Hyakka to protect Yoshiwara.
日輪を守るためじゃ｡
It was to protect Hinowa.
そして 晴太… ぬしは➡
And Seita...
You are the existence that Hinowa protected with her life.
その日輪が
命を賭して守ろうとした存在｡
吉原で 子を生めば
その 母も子も 始末される｡
Giving birth in Yoshiwara...
means that both mother and child are to be killed.
それでも ぬしは
この世に生まれた｡
In spite of that, you were born unto this world.
吉原から逃げ出せば
地の果てまで追いつめられ➡
If she escapes from Yoshiwara,
no matter where she runs to, she will be found and dealt with.
必ず 始末される｡
それでも ぬしは
地上に連れ出された｡
In spite of that, she still brought you up to the surface.
((手下:子供がいません！
The child's not here.
Look's like the child's been handed over to someone else.
すでに どこかに
引き渡したのかと…｡
殺しな｡ あの子を
この手に抱いたときから➡
Kill me.
From the moment I held that child,
覚悟はできてるよ｡
I've been mentally prepared.
(鳳仙)残念だったな｡
まだ 楽にはさせんぞ｡
It's unfortunate...
but I can't let you off the hook just yet.
ｷｻﾏには 死ぬまで
あの地獄で苦しんでもらう｡
You shall suffer in that hell until the day you die.
まだまだ
利用価値もあることだしな｡
After all, you still have plenty of value to me.
I'm not joking around!
(日輪)冗談じゃないよ｡
ｱﾝﾀの操り人形は
もう まっぴら御免さ｡
I shall be your puppet...
no longer!
わからんのか？ すべては
お前次第だということが｡
You still don't get it?
Everything depends on you!
たかが ﾜｯﾊﾟ１人
見逃すことは 容易な話だ｡
I'm willing to let a mere child go.
だが 橋の下を調べ➡
But... I'm also willing to search under the bridge and kill that old geezer and the kid.
その じじいごと
ﾜｯﾊﾟを斬り捨てるのも➡
また 容易な話だ｡
さぁ どちらか ひとつ
選ぶがいい))
Now...
what is it going to be?
(月詠)わっちらにとって 日輪は➡
Just as Hinowa illuminated the everlasting night for us,
常夜を照らす太陽だったように➡
日輪にとって 晴太…
ぬしも 特別な存在だったのじゃ｡
To Hinowa... you are a special existence, Seita.
太陽は 晴天でなければ輝けぬ｡
The Sun cannot shine without clear skies.
わっちは ぬしを
死なせるわけにはいかぬ｡
I cannot allow you to die here.
帰れ｡ ぬしが死ねば➡
Go home.
If you die,
日輪の
今までの辛苦が 水泡に帰す！
Hinowa's suffering will all have been in vain.
ん？ おい
過分な心遣い 痛み入るがね｡
Oi, we really appreciate your concern,
どうやら もう手遅れらしいぜ｡
but it looks like it's too late.
傘… まさか… あれ!?
An umbrella?
Don't tell me...
That's...
♪♪～
T-That...
あ… あれは… あの傘は…｡
That umbrella is...
A Yato?
夜兎!? なんで…
なんで こんなところに夜兎族が!?
Why?
Why are there Yato clan members here?
どうやら せっかく用意してくれた
ｱﾝﾀの逃げ道も➡
Looks like the escape route you prepared for us...
手が 回っていたようだぜ｡
違う｡
is already under their control.
No...
あれは 鳳仙の回し者じゃない｡
He's not Housen's subordinate.
あれは…｡
(阿伏兎)ｶﾞｷをよこせ｡
He's...
Hand the brat over.
Hand that brat over to me.
(阿伏兎)
そのｶﾞｷを こちらによこせ｡
G-Gin-chan, this is bad.
ぎ… 銀ちゃん… やばいｱﾙ｡
ｱｲﾂ とびきり
やばい匂いがするｱﾙ｡
That guy gives me a very bad feeling.
血の匂い…
幾多の戦場を生き抜き➡
The stench of blood...
He's covered in the smell of the blood of countless people.
染み込んできた 血の匂い｡
本物の 夜兎の匂い｡
The smell of a true Yato.
なんで… こんなところに…｡
Why is he here?
♪♪～
(月詠)早く！
今のうちに 逃げろ!!
Hurry!
Nows your chance!
Run!
♪♪～
月詠さん!!
Tsukuyo-san!
下から!?
From below?!
♪♪～
銀ちゃん!!
Gin-chan!
♪♪～
夜兎が ２人…？
There are two Yato?!
ｸｿｯ… 離せっ!!
Dammit! Let me go!
晴太～っ!!
Seita!
(神威)ｼﾞｬﾏだ｡ どいてくれよ｡
Move.
Get out of the way.
言ったはずだ｡
I already told you...
弱いﾔﾂに 用はないって…｡
I don't give a damn...
about weaklings!
♪♪～
Bro-
神楽～っ!!
Kagura!
銀さ～ん！ みんな～!!
Gin-san! Everybody!
(阿伏兎)やりすぎたかね｡
I think we went overboard.
うるさい じいさんに
どやされそうだ｡
We're gonna get yelled at by that annoying geezer.
(神威)大丈夫だよ｡
It's fine.
鳳仙の旦那は こんな街より
花魁様に ご執心だ｡
Master Housen holds the courtesans of higher value than this city.
この子を連れていけば
機嫌も直る｡
If we bring him the kid, I'm sure he'll be in a better mood.
それに これくらいやらなきゃ
死ぬﾔﾂじゃないんでね｡
And besides,
if you don't go this far, she won't die.
ん？ 知り合いでもいたか？
Hmm? You know one of them?
いや… もう関係ないや｡
No.
It's none of my business anymore.
(激突音)
みんな 無事ですか？
Is everyone alright?
Kagura!
神楽！ しっかりしろ！
Hang in there! Oi, Kagura!
おい！ 神楽!!
晴太君が… ｱｲﾂら…
ｱｲﾂら いったい…｡
Seita-kun was taken by those guys...
Who were they?
おそらく ﾔﾂら… 春雨じゃ｡
Most likely, they're...
from Harusame.
春雨!? 春雨って
あの 宇宙海賊 春雨!?
Harusame?! You mean the Harusame space pirates?!
天正教の密売に絡み
ﾎﾞｸらと戦ったり…➡
They're more than just drug traffickers.
We've fought them before!
紅桜のときに
鬼兵隊と手を組んで➡
During the Benizakura incident,
they cooperated with the Kiheitai against Katsura-san's group.
桂さんたちの前に現れた…｡
吉原の遊女たちは
親に売られた者も多いが➡
Although many of the prostitutes in Yoshiwara were sold off by their parents,
その多くは
不当な人身売買によって➡
there are many more who end up in Yoshiwara as victims of human trafficking.
吉原へ流れついた者｡
その利権に 古くから
深く関わっているのが➡
The Harusame space pirates have established their interest in this place since long ago.
宇宙海賊 春雨｡
いや 関わるどころか
吉原の楼主 夜王鳳仙こそ➡
No... it's much more than mere interest...
Yoshiwara's owner, Night King Housen,
春雨で 幹部を務めていた男｡
was a former high-ranking official of Harusame.
夜王鳳仙… ﾔﾂが
そう呼ばれているのは➡
Night King Housen.
He's called this...
この 常夜の国の
主であるがためだけではない｡
not only because of his lordship over the land of everlasting night.
光に嫌われた一族｡
夜を生きる者たち｡
The clan forsaken by the Sun...
The ones who live in the shadows...
それを統べる者｡ 夜を統べる者｡
The one controlling them...
The one controlling the shadows...
The Night King Housen,
夜王鳳仙とは
夜兎の王と呼ばれた男のことよ｡
is the man who was once known as the King of the Yato.
や… 夜兎の王だって!?
The King of the Yato?!
夜王は 有象無象の強者が
ひしめく夜兎の中で➡
Amongst the countless Yato warriors, the Night King was one of the most powerful.
一大勢力を築いていた
実力者だったんじゃ｡
あの最強の掃除屋…➡
He could even go up against the strongest assassin, Umibouzu.
星海坊主と
並び称されるほどのな｡
あのﾊｹﾞと…｡
Against that baldy.
どうやら ｵﾚたちは
とんでもねえﾊﾞｹﾓﾉに➡
Looks like we're messing with some kind of monster.
ｹﾝｶ ふっかけちまったみてえだな｡
G-Gin-chan...
ぎ… 銀ちゃん…｡
神楽ちゃん！
ﾎﾝﾄに やばいのは➡
Kagura-chan!
The really dangerous one...
ｿｲﾂじゃないね…｡
息子が いるｱﾙ｡
isn't him.
The baldy...
そのﾊｹﾞの…｡
has a son.
私の ﾊﾞｶ兄貴が！
He's my...
moron of a brother!
To be continued
A mutiny?
Kamui, you don't believe in hierarchies.
You only believe in the difference between the strong and the weak.
You would even bare your fangs against your master.
[Butting into A Fight is Dangerous"]
[Yato vs Yato, Hosen vs Kamui!!]
["Those two were once master and pupil..."]